Erwin Panofsky
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1921-1978, undated, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-16; 16 linear ft. Reels 2108-2128)
  - Colleagues, Scholars, Students and Other Individuals, 1921-1978, undated, 1.1:
    - M, General (single letters, Magallón - Mylonas), 1932-1968, (2 folders) (Box 8, Reel 2117)
      Mayekawa, Seiro
      Mayer, Martin
      Mendel, Arthur
      Merlen, L. Jacobs van
      Merkel
      Merle, Pierre
      Messerer, Wilhelm
      Metternich, Franz Graf Wolff
      Meurer, Heribert
      Meyer, Ann Mans
      Meyer, Erich
      Meyer, Herman
      Meyer-Baer, Kathi
      Meyers, Hans
      Millar, Bradford P.
      Miller, Charles R. D.
      Miller, Clyde R.
      Misch, Georg
      Moehle, Ruediger
      Moeller, Kurt
      Molle, F. Van
      Mondadori, Alberto
      Montagna, Lino
      Montago, Jennifer
      Montesquiou Frzensac, Blaise de
      Montone, Father
      Moratz, Frank
      Morawitz, Kurt
      Morris, Dudley H.
      Morse, Beverly
      Mortimer, Mary H.
      Moseley, Jane E.
      Moulinier, Edward P.
      Müller, Gerhard
      Mullet, Charles F.
      Munhall, Edgar J.
      Münzel, B.H.M.
      Mutsaers, B.
      Mylonas, George E.
    - Maas - Manasse, 1955-1968 (Box 8, Reel 2117)
      Maas, John C.
      Mabille, A.
      Mack-Smith, Denis
      Mahon, Denis
      Majno, Guido
      Malone, Lee
      Manasse, Ernst Moritz
    - Mandowsky - Martin, 1925-1968, undated (Box 8, Reel 2117-2118)
      Mandowsky, Erna
      Mann, Alfred
      Marcus, Stanley
      Marenau, Henry
      Marquand, Eleanor C.
      Marsden, C. A.
      Martens, Bella
      Martin, F. David
    - Martin, John Rupert, 1952-1967 (Box 8, Reel 2117-2118)
    - Martin - Meeson, 1947-1966 (Box 8, Reel 2117-2118)
      Martin, Kurt
      Mather, Frank J., Jr.
      Mayo, Penelope C.
      Mayor, A. Hyatt
      Meeson, B.
    - Meiss, Millard, 1936-1975, undated, (4 folders) (Box 8, Reel 2117-2118)
    - Melamed - Mendel, 1950-1966 (Box 8, Reel 2117-2118)
      Melamed, Hope Goodman
      Meller, P. Peter
      Meltzoff, Stanley
      Menase, Luc
    - Menil - Meyerson, 1952-1967 (Box 8, Reel 2117-2118)
      Menil, John de
      Merritt, Benjamin
      Mertz, Richard R.
      Metzger, Mendel
      Meyerson, I.
    - Meyne - Middledorf, 1944-1962 (Box 8, Reel 2117-2118)
      Meyne, Willi
      Middledorf, Ulrich
    - Miner, Dorothy Eugenia, 1935-1973 (Box 8, Reel 2117-2118)
    - Minott - Mitchell, 1957-1966 (Box 8, Reel 2117-2118)
      Minott, Charles I.
      Mirimonde, A. P. de
      Mirsky, Jeannette
      Mitchell, Charles
    - Mitrany, David, 1952-1965 (Box 8, Reel 2117-2118)
    - Moakley, Gertrude, 1955-1967 (Box 8, Reel 2117-2118)
    - Modestini - Möhle, 1957-1965 (Box 8, Reel 2117-2118)
      Modestini, Mario
      Möhle, Hans
    - Möller, Lise Lotte, 1954-1967 (Box 8, Reel 2117-2118)
    - Mommsen - Morey, 1942-1961 (Box 9, Reel 2118)
      Mommsen, Theodor E.
      Mongan, Agnes
      Mink, Samuel H.
      Morey, Charles Rufus
    - Morley - Mosse, 1947-1966 (Box 9, Reel 2118)
      Morley, S. Griswold
      Morper, Johann Joseph
      Morse, Marston
      Mortimer, M. H.
      Mosse, Walter
    - Mueller - Mufmord, 1951-1967 (Box 9, Reel 2118)
      Mueller, Earl
      Müller, Theodor
      Müller, Wolfgang J.
      Müller Hofstede, Cornelius
      Mumford, Lewis
    - Muraro, Michelangelo, 1956-1967 (Box 9, Reel 2118)
    - Mütherich, Florentine, 1960-1966 (Box 9, Reel 2118)
    - N, General (single letters, Nachod - Nostrand), 1937-1966 (Box 9, Reel 2118)
      Nachod, Frederick C.
      Najder, Zdzislaw
      Nathan, Otto
      Nauert, Charles G., Jr.
      Neisser, H.
      Nemser, Cindy
      Neuberger, Hans
      Neumann, Sigmund
      New York Times
      Newton, Francis J.
      Nicely, Katharine
      Nickerson, Hoffman
      Nicolson, L. Vertova
      Nicolson, Mary Coe
      Nilgren, Ursula
      Nill, Anna M.
      Niver, Charles
      Norden, Heinz
      Nostrand, Albert Van
    - Nadel - Nef, 1944-1967 (Box 9, Reel 2118)
      Nadel, George H.
      Nahm, Milton C.
      Nash, Ray
      Nathan, Hans
      Nathan, Helmuth
      Nef, John U.
    - Negri - Neumann, 1936-1971, undated (Box 9, Reel 2118)
      Negri, Enrico and Lilo de
      Nesselhauf, Herbert, undated
      Neugebauer, Otto
      Neumann, Jaromír
    - Neumeyer, Alfred, 1943-1970 (Box 9, Reel 2118)
    - Newtib - Nock, 1948-1970 (Box 9, Reel 2118)
      Newton, Caroline
      Nicolson, Marjorie H.
      Nock, Arthur D.
    - Nordenfalk, Carl, 1939-1967, (5 folders) (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
    - Nordström - Norton, 1953-1967 (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
    - Nordström, Carl-Otto, 1953-1967 (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
    - Nordström, Folke, 1953-1963 (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
    - Norton, Paul F., 1956-1966 (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
    - O, General (single letters, O'Brien - Opie), 1933-1967 (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
      O'Brien, Gerard F.
      O'Dea, Connie
      Oelher, Lisa
      Oertal, Robert
      Offenbacher, Emil
      Oksala, P.
      Olin, Caroline Bower
      Opie, J. N. Lindsay
    - Oberer - Offner, 1931-1968 (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
      Oberer, Hariolf
      O'Connell, Rev. John P.
      Oexmann, Theophila Joan
      Offner, Richard
    - Ong, Rev. Father Walter J., 1956-1957 (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
    - Oppenheimer, 1960-1966 (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
      Oppenheimer, Fritz E.
      Oppenheimer, J. Robert
    - Orsini, Gian, 1954-1966, undated (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
    - Osten, Gert van, 1952-1972, (2 folders) (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
    - Owen, Henry G., 1956-1966 (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
    - P, General (single letters, Paine - Pulitzer), 1937-1967 (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
      Paine, Francisca Warren
      Paine, Michael J.
      Palacios, Alvar Gonzalez
      Palmer, George A.
      Pancoast, John
      Papajewski, Helmut
      Pargellis, Stanley
      Park, Marion S.
      Parker, Harry S., III
      Parsons, Harold W.
      Partington, Ruth
      Paul, Jurgen
      Pauwels, H.
      Pawson, Herbert B.
      Pevsner, Nikolaus
      Philippe, Joseph
      Philippsohn, Jenny
      Picard, Charles
      Picard, Raymond
      Pierson, Mrs. Emery Lancaster
      Pinthus, Alexander
      Poillon, Mrs. Arthur
      Polier, Justine Wise
      Polzer, Joseph
      Pompanin, A.
      Poole, Dewitt Clinton
      Popesco, Paul
      Post, Chandler R.
      Preddy, C. R., Jr.
      Price, Derek J.
      Price, Pamela
      Princeton Club of New York
      Prudential Insurance Company
      Puhst, Johann
      Pulitzer, Joseph
    - Paatz - Pächt, 1951-1967 (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
      Paatz, W.
      Pächt, Otto
    - Pais - Papp, 1953-1967 (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
      Pais, Abraham
      Palme, Per
      Panofsky, Hans and Wolfgang
      Papp, Béla
    - Parkhurst, Charles P., 1943-1971 (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
    - Pásztory, Catherine, 1949-1966 (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
    - Pauli, 1928-1970, undated (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
      Pauli, Gustav
      Pauli, Magdalene
      Pauli, Wolfgang
    - Paulsson, Gregor, 1952-1960 (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
    - Pacchiai - Petersen, 1947-1967 (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
      Pacchiai, Pió
      Pedretti, Carlo
      Peery, William
      Perlmutter, Joshua
      Perrig, Alexander, F. X.
      Petersen, Ulla
    - Peyre - Phillips, 1949-1967 (Box 9, Reel 2118-2119)
      Peyre, Henri M.
      Pfeiffer, H.
      Philip, Lotte Brandt
      Philippot, Paul
      Phillips, John
    - Pichetto - Plaut, 1948-1966 (Box 10, Reel 2119)
      Pichetto, Stephen G.
      Pieper, Paul
      Piper, Otto A.
      Placzek, George
      Plaut, Alfred
    - Plochmann - Pope-Hennessy, 1938-1968 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Plochmann, George Kimball
      Pobor, Grga
      Poggioli, Renato
      Pölnitz, Gerhard Freiherr von
      Pope-Hennessy, John
    - Porcher, Jean, 1947-1968 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
    - Posner - Puyvelde, 1942-1967 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Posner, Donald
      Post, Gaines
      Pratt, Robert A.
      Pressouyre, Léon
      Preston, Lionel
      Procacci, Ugo
      Puppi, Lionello
      Puyvelde, Leo van
    - Quarré - Qvarnström, 1946-1968 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Quarré, Pierre
      Quintavalle, Augusta G.
      Quirt, Walter W.
      Qvarnström, Gunnar
    - R, General (single letters, Rabuse - Ryskamp), 1938-1967 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Rabuse, Georg
      Radernaher, Hans
      Rakob, Friederich
      Rappolt, Paul
      Rasmussen, Nils Ludvig
      Rand, E. K.
      Reading, Carolyn
      Reed, Sue Welsh
      Reibnitz, Rudolf V.
      Reincke, Heinrich
      Reissner, H. G.
      Reimche, Jean
      Revel, E.
      Reynal, Eugene
      RIAS
      Richter, George M.
      Richter, Gisela M. A.
      Rieck, Wilhelm
      Riedl, Peter Anselm
      Rieth,, Adolf
      Riggio, Conrad F.
      Ringbom, Sixten
      Ringler, Josef
      Ritter, Ewald
      Robinson, Chalfant
      Rodríguez Savall, Alfonso
      Roems, H.
      Rose, Elsa
      Rood, Sherrill M.
      Rookmaaker, H. R.
      Roosen-Runge, H.
      Rorimer, James J.
      Rosenbach, A. S.
      Rosenbaum, Elizabeth
      Rosenberg, C. G.
      Rosenberg, Frances
      Rosenbert, Mr. and Mrs. John
      Rosenfeld, Leonard J.
      Rosenthal, Jane
      Ross, James Bruce
      Ross, Lawrence J.
      Roth, Cecil
      Rowley, George
      Rubin, Enid
      Rückert, Ranier
      Raudruf, L.
      Ruhemann, Helmut
      Rutan, Clinton N.
      Ryskamp, Charles
    - Rabb - Raemisch, 1949-1967 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Rabb, Theodore K.
      Rabinowicz, Theodore
      Rademacher, Hans
      Raemisch, Waldemar
    - Raggio, Olga, 1951-1965 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
    - Randall - Raubitschek, 1940-1967 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Randall, Lewis V.
      Randall, Lillian M. C.
      Raubitschek, Antony E.
    - Rawson - Reff, 1951-1967 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Rawson, C. J.
      Reese, Gustav
      Reff, Theodore
    - Regteren - Reinhold, 1945-1965 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Regteren Altena, J. Q. van
      Reinhart, Oskar
      Reinheldt, Curt
      Reinhold, H. A.
    - Reti, Ladislao, 1957-1973 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
    - Reutersvärd, 1957-1965 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Reutersvärd, Oscar
      Reutersvärd, Patrick
    - Rewald - Richter, 1937-1966 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Rewald, John
      Reynolds, Robert L.
      Reznicek, E.K.J.
      Richelson, Paul W.
      Richmond, Donald E.
      Richter, Irma A.
    - Rickert, Margaret, 1936-1950 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
    - Ripley, Elisabeth, 1957 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
    - Robb, David M., 1936-1962 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
    - Roberts - Roosval, 1946-1967, undated (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Roberts, R. M.
      Robertson, Giles
      Roche, Thomas P., Jr.
      Roe, Albert
      Romanini, Angiola Maria
      Roosval, Johnny
    - Rosen - Rosenberg, 1954-1967, undated (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Rosen, Edward
      Rosenau-Carmi, Helen
      Rosenbaum, Allen
      Rosenberg, J. B.
    - Rosenberg - Rosenthal, 1946-1962, undated (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Rosenberg, Jakob
      Rosenberg, Pierre
      Rosenblum, Robert
      Rosenthal, Erwin
      Rosenthal, Gertrude
    - Rosenwald, Lessing J., 1951-1965 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
    - Röthel, Hans K., 1932-1971 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
    - Rothlein - Röthlisberger, 1952-1964 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Rothlein, Jerome
      Röthlisberger, Marcel
    - Rowland - Ruzicka, 1948-1965 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Rowland, Benjamin
      Rudenstine, Angelica
      Rudzinski, Aleksander Witold
      Russell, Heide
      Rüstow, Alexander
      Ruzicka, R.
    - S, General (single letters, Saalman - Silvers), 1937-1967, (2 folders) (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Saalman, Howard
      Saint-Aubain, M. P. de
      Salaquarda, Charles
      Sales, Grover, Jr.
      Salinger, Gerhard
      Salm, Christian Altgraf
      Salomon, Albert
      Sandbla, Nils G.
      Sanders, Ernst H.
      Sanders, Gabe
      Sanford, Eva Matthews
      Savage, H. L.
      Scheidmantelivian J.
      Schelldorfer, K.
      Scher, Stephen K.
      Schickel, Richard
      Schildt-Bunim, M.
      Schmalenbach, Fritz
      Schmidt, Georg
      Schmidt, H. D.
      Schmidt-Degener, H.
      Schneider, Donald D.
      Scholtens, H.J.J.
      Schrader, Jack L.
      Schramm, Percy Ernst
      Schreinert Kurt
      Schrickel, H. G.
      Schubert, Wolf H.
      Schuchhardt, W. H.
      Schütt, Mary
      Schütze, Martin
      Schultz, H. Stefan
      Schulz, Juergen
      Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation
      Schwartz, Gary
      Schwartz, James H.
      Secchi, Claudio Cesare
      [Sessions?], Roger
      Shearman, John K. G.
      Siebenhüner, H.
      Siegel, Eli
      Siegerist, Henry E.
      Silvers, Ilse Folk
    - S, General (single letters, Silverstein - Szathmary), 1944-1967 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Silverstein, Mary
      Silz, Priscilla
      Simon, Erika
      Simor, George
      Singleton, Charles S.
      Sinicins, N.
      Sjöqvist, Erik
      Slingenberg
      Sloane, John P.
      Smith, Francis P.
      Smith, Graham
      Smith, Nancy R.
      Smith, Richard Flanders
      Smulders, F.
      Snyers, M. R.
      Snyder, Robert
      Solomon, Dagmar I.
      Solomon, Eva aTevan
      Solomonski, Fritz
      Spear, Richard E.
      Spector, Jack
      Speigel, Eileen
      Sptizer, Wolfgang
      Stampflel, Felice
      Stange, Alfred
      Stapleforth, Richard W.
      Stebbins, Frederick A.
      Steinhausen, H. K.
      Stern, Frederic A.
      Stern, Otto
      Sternfeld, W.
      Stevens, Charles Rolfe
      Stewart, Dorothy N.
      Stites, Raymond S.
      Stoessel, Oskar
      Stone, I. F.
      Strauss, Walter L.
      Strayer, Joseph R.
      Strong, Earl D.
      Strunsky, Robert
      Sulzberger, Susanne
      Sztuki, Pa stwowe Zbiory
      Szablowski, Jerzy
      Szathmary, Arthur
    - Sachs - Salas, 1948-1969 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Sachs, Curt
      Sachs, David
      Sachs, Paul J.
      Saffaro, Lucio
      Salas, Xavier de
    - Saldern - Salmi, 1940-1967 (Box 10, Reel 2119-2120)
      Saldern, Axel von
      Salinger, Herman
      Salmi, Mario
    - Salomon, Richard, 1934-1968, undated, (4 folders) (Box 10, Reel 2120-2121)
    - Santillana - Saran, 1956-1967, undated (Box 10, Reel 2120-2121)
      Santillana, Giurio de
      Santos, Reynaldo dos
      Saran, Bernhard
    - Sarollli - Sarton, 1946-1967 (Box 10, Reel 2120-2121)
      Sarolli, Gian Roberto
      Sarton, George
    - Sauerländer, Willibald, 1957-1967 (Box 10, Reel 2120-2121)
    - Sauerlandt - Scaglia, 1921-1969, undated (Box 11, Reel 2121)
      Sauerlandt, Max
      Saxl, Fritz
      Scaglia, Gustina
    - Schaefer, Claude, 1947-1966 (Box 11, Reel 2121)
    - Schaper, Gunter, 1962 (Box 11, Reel 2121)
    - Schapiro, Meyer, 1937-1967 (Box 11, Reel 2121)
    - Schaut, Father Quentin L., 1948-1961 (Box 11, Reel 2121)
    - Schefold - Schiff, 1958-1972, undated (Box 11, Reel 2121)
      Schefold, Marianne, 1958-1965
      Schéle, Sune, 1962
      Schenk zu Schweinsberg, Eberhard Freiherr
      Schiff, Gert
    - Schilling - Schönberger, 1945-1966 (Box 11, Reel 2121)
      Schilling, E.
      Schilling, Rosy
      Schlunk, Helmut
      Schmid, Wolfgang
      Schmidt, Gerhard
      Schönberger, G.
    - Schöne, Wolfgang, 1954-1967 (Box 11, Reel 2121)
    - Schrade - Schuchhardt, 1927-1976 (Box 11, Reel 2121)
      Schrade, Hubert
      Schramm, Ruth
      Schryver, Antoine de
    - Schulz-Behrend - Schwabacher, 1954-1968 (Box 11, Reel 2121)
      Schulz-Behrend, George
      Schürer-von Witzleben, Elisabeth
      Schüssler, Hermann
      Schwabacher, Willy
    - Schwarz, 1953-1974 (Box 11, Reel 2121)
      Schwarz, Heinrich
      Schwarz, Henry F.
    - Schwarzenberg - Seidlin, 1946-1966, undated (Box 11, Reel 2121)
      Schwarzenberg, Erkinger
      Schweitzer, Bernhard
      Segall, Berta
      Seidlin, Oskar
    - Selig - Serra, 1947-1967 (Box 11, Reel 2121)
      Selig, Karl Ludwig
      Seligmann, Germain
      Serra, Manuel
    - Sessions - Setton, 1950-1967, undated (Box 11, Reel 2121)
      Sessions, Barbara
      Settis, Salvatore
      Setton, Kenneth M.
    - Šev enko - Seymour, 1947-1965 (Box 11, Reel 2121)
      Šev enko, Ihor
      Sewall, John
      Sexton, Eric H. L.
      Seymour, Charles
    - Seyrig - Sheppard, 1946-1968 (Box 11, Reel 2121)
      Seyrig, Henri
      Sheldon, Alice D.
      Sheppard, Carl D.
    - Sherry, William Grant, 1961-1964 (Box 11, Reel 2121)
    - Shorr - Sjöquist, 1938-1967 (Box 11, Reel 2121)
      Shorr, Dorothy
      Shyrock, Richard H.
      Silverstein, Theodore
      Simon, Jules
      Simson, Otto von
      Sjöquist, Erik
    - Sladeczek - Smith, 1951-1967, undated (Box 11, Reel 2121)
      Sladeczek, Leonhard
      Sloane, Joseph C.
      Smith, Nancy and E. Baldwin
    - Smyth, Craig, 1951-1966, (2 folders) (Box 11, Reel 2121)
    - Snell, Bruno, 1946-1971, undated (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
    - Snyder - Solberg, 1950-1963 (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
      Snyder, James E.
      Solberg, Carl
    - Somitz, Walter and Elly, 1928-1963, undated (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
    - Sommer - Soth, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
    - Sommer, Frank H., 1954-1955 (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
    - Soper, Alexander Coburn, 1949-1953 (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
    - Soth, Lauren, 1963-1967 (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
    - Speiser, David, 1960-1967 (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
    - Spencer, 1951-1964 (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
      Spencer, Eleanor P.
      Spencer, John R.
    - Speilberg, Ernest and Marie-Louise, 1951-1966 (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
    - Spitzer, Leo, 1950-1956, undated (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
    - Springell - Starobinski, 1956-1965 (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
      Springell, F.
      Stafski, Heinz
      Starobinski, Jean
    - Stechow, W., 1922-1971, (3 folders) (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
    - Steck - Steinberg, 1940-1966 (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
      Steck, Max
      Steegmuller, Francis
      Steinberg, Leo
    - Steinitz, Kate, 1945-1967 (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
    - Sterling - Steneberg, 1954-1966 (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
      Sterling, Charles
      Steneberg, Karl Eric
    - Stern, Henri, 1954-1967 (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
    - Sternfeld, Frederick W., 1950-1961 (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
    - Stillman - Strauss, 1931-1968, undated (Box 11, Reel 2121-2122)
      Stillman, Clark
      Stock, Brian
      Stoddard, Whitney S.
      Stokes, Muriel
      Stone, Lawrence
      Straus, Erwin W.
      Strauss, Lewis
    - Streisand - Stridbeck, 1953-1965 (Box 12, Reel 2122)
      Streisand, Hugo
      Stridbeck, Carl G.
    - Strittmatter - Suida, 1950-1967 (Box 12, Reel 2122)
      Strittmatter, Rev. Anselm
      Stubbe, Wolf
      Stubblebine, James H.
      Suida, W.
    - Swarzesnki, Georg, 1930-1957 (Box 12, Reel 2122)
    - Swarzenski, Hanus, 1931-1966 (Box 12, Reel 2122)
    - Sweeney - Szladitz, 1937-1967 (Box 12, Reel 2122)
      Sweeney, J. J.
      Swoboda, Karl M.
      Symeonides, Sibilla
      Szladitz, Lola
    - T, General (single letters, Takashina - Tyler), 1940-1967 (Box 12, Reel 2122)
      Takashina, Suji
      Tavel, Hans Christoph von
      Taylor, Michael A.
      Teasdale, Molly
      Ternbach, Joseph
      Theuerkauff-Leiderwald, Anna Elisabeth
      Thirby, Mrs. Edwin L.
      Thirlwall, John C.
      Thompson, Dorothy
      Thordeman, Bengt
      Thorne, Edgar F.
      Thullier, Jacques
      Tigerstedt, E. N.
      Tolman, Sally Jones
      Tomko, George Peter
      Tördten, Hans W.
      Toussiant, Rolf
      Tritscher, Walther
      Tritsch
      Turner, R.
      Tyler, Parker
    - Tarkington, Booth and Betty, 1938-1973, undated, (2 folders) (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
    - Tatarkiewicz - TenBroeck, 1937-1965 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
      Tatarkiewicz, Wlodyslaw
      Taubert, Johannes
      Taylor, Francis Henry
      Taylor, Sybil
      Temkin, Oswei
      Temko, Allan
      TenBroeck, Carl and Jane
    - Tervarent, Guy de, 1956-1966 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
    - Teyssèdre - Thompson, 1951-1967 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
      Teyssèdre, Bernard
      Thiem, Gunther
      Thompson, C. R.
      Thompson, Homer A.
      Thompson, Mary Lee
    - Thordeman - Thyssen-Bornemisza, 1961-1966 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
      Thyssen-Bornemisza, H. H.
    - Tietze, Erica, 1937-1958 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
    - Tolnay - Trinkaus, 1940-1966 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
      Tolnay, Charles de
      Tonelli, Giorgio
      Trapp. J. B.
      Trell, Bluma L.
      Treves, Marco
      Trinkaus, Charles
    - Tschmelitsch - Usher, 1950-1968 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
      Tschmelitsch, Günther
      Tselos, Dimitri
      Tilly, Mary Ann
      Tuve, Rosemund
      Ullman, B. L.
      Ullman, Pierre
      Ullmann, Ernst
      Underwood, Margaret
      Ungar, Emery U.
      Urken, Mrs. Paul
      Usher, Abbott P.
    - Van Isselt - Voss (single letters), 1942-1967 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
      Van Isselt, Harriette Van Dam
      Van de Velde, R. W.
      Van Doren, Irita
      Van Ghent, Dorothy
      Vanderbilt, Paul
      Verodn, Timothy C.
      Vescovini, G. Federici
      Vidal, Adrienne
      Viljoen, Helen Gill
      Viñals, Salvio G.
      Vogel, Amos
      Vogel, Bernard W.
      Vogel, Gerhard
      Vogelsang, W.
      Vogelstein, Hertha
      Volbach, Walther R.
      Vondracek, M. Jon
      Von Saldern, A.
      Voss, W.
    - Valentiner - Vasalle, 1942-166 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
      Valentiner, W. R.
      Van Kuylen, Krister
      Van Nostrand, A. D.
      Varma, K. M.
      Vasalle, Rudolph A.
    - Veblen, Oswald, 1950-1960 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
    - Verdier, Philippe, 1949-1967 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
    - Verhaegen, Nicole, 1951-1960 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
    - Verheyen, Egon, 1960-1967, (3 folders) (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
    - Verulam, Lord, 1951-1953 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
    - Vetter, Ewald M., 1955-1966 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
    - Vierbeck, Peter, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
    - Vinken, P. J., 1957-1964 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
    - Vöge, Wilhelm, 1924-1975, undated, (3 folders) (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
    - Vossler, Otto, 1953-1955 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
    - W, General (single letters, Waith - Wülfingen), 1926-1967 (Box 12, Reel 2122-2123)
      Waith, Eugene M.
      Walle, A. Van de
      Wallen, Burr
      Wallington, Ian
      Wallis, Mieczyslaro
      Walters, Christian
      Walters, Gary
      Warburg, Erich M.
      Ward, John L.
      Ward, Mary C.
      Watson, George
      Wabinski, Zygmunt
      WBAI Radio
      Weadock, Gertrude
      Wearinga, Juw fon
      Weber-Marshall, J.
      Webster, Carson
      Wehle, Harry
      Weil, André
      Weilgart, Wolfgang J.
      Weinberg, Saul
      Weinberg, Gladys D.
      Weinberger, Edith
      Weingram, S.
      Weintraub, Viktor
      Weisgall, Nathalie
      Weisinger, Herbert
      Weisner, Ulrich
      Weitz, Morris
      Wesenberg, Rudolf
      While, Roy
      White, Christopher
      White, Howard B.
      Whitman, Robert F.
      Whitney, Hassler
      WHOM Radio
      Wickman, E. K.
      Wight, Frederick S.
      Wilber, Donald N.
      Wilde, Johannes
      Wildenstein, Daniel
      Wiles, R. M.
      Willard, Helen D.
      Wellliver, Warman
      Williams, Phyllis L.
      Willoughby, Harold R.
      Wilson, J. Christy
      Winslow, Harriet P.
      Winternitz, Emanuel
      Wirth, Karl-August
      Witt, Eobert
      Wohl, Hellmut
      Wolandt, Gerd
      Wolf, Gertrude
      Wolff, Eleanor L.
      Wolff, Helene
      Wood, Ledger
      Woodward
      Woody, William H., Jr.
      Woolf, Harry
      Wülfngen, Ordenberg Bock von
    - Waal - Wackernagel, 1947-1964 (Box 12, Reel 2123-2123)
      Waal, H. van de
      Wace, Allen J. B.
      Wackernagel, Wolfgang D.
    - Walker, 1948-1966 (Box 13, Reel 2124)
      Walker, D. P.
      Walker, John